[Music]
Today we're talking about one of our
favorite sleep tools, the Temper Erggo
Pro Smart Power Base.
>> The number one factor in the quality of
your sleep is the quality of your
routine. Go to bed at the same time,
wake up at the same time. Keep your
bedroom cool, 67° or below, and create a
calming sleep sanctuary.
>> When you first get into bed, raise your
legs just a little bit. This relieves
pressure on your lower back and hips and
gets your circulation moving.
>> Then elevate your head and back to
breathe easier, reduce stress, and prep
your body for sleep. You'll feel the
difference right away.
>> The Pro Smart Base takes all of that to
the next level with these amazing
features. Full range of ergonomic
positions for head, feet, and everything
in between. Plus a lumbar adjustment
with an added lift in the lower back for
those who need the extra spinal support.
Waveform Massage is the very best
vibration massage available today. It's
powered by sound waves and is a relaxing
experience that transmits comfort
through the entire mattress. Snore
Response detects snoring and
automatically raises the head of the bed
about 12° without waking either sleeper.
Sleep coaching tracks your sleep
patterns and gives you insights and
routines to help improve your rest. And
soundscape mode is a built-in audio
system to play soothing nature sounds,
white noise, or even your own playlist
to help your body and mind wind down.
>> This isn't just a fancy adjustable bed.
It's a wellness machine. It's like
having a chiropractor, yoga instructor,
and sleep coach all built into your bed.
>> Whether you're sleeping, recovering,
watching TV, or reading, it really just
makes the whole bedtime experience
better.
>> Find your best rest with ProSmart.
[Music]